Finding Aid for the Mort Fine Papers PASC.0076
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Radio Projects, (1946-1959); Boxes 22-31, 38-45, 48-49, 53, 66, 70
  - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar: Starlet Matter (The), 1953 Jan 16 (Box 49)
- Television Projects, (ca. 1950-1982)
  The series is arranged alphabetically by program titles.
  The Television Projects are scripts primarily in bound volumes. Television programs represented include I Spy, Kojak, The Manhunter, The Most Deadly Game, and Streets of San Francisco, among others. Additionally there is a small amount of clippings and ephemera related to I Spy.
  - ABC Movie of the Week: River of Gold (The), 1970 Sept 28 (Box 46)
    In bound volume labeled Free Lance TV Scripts.
  - Access and Trial: Scar on the Sand, 1963 Apr 9 (Box 27)
  - Aquanauts (The): Episode 12B, 1960 Aug 30 (Box 54)
    Working title: Underwater Volcano. In bound volume labeled The Aquanauts.
  - Aquanauts (The): Episode 14B, 1960 Sept 20 (Box 54)
    Working title: Arms of Venus. In bound volume labeled The Aquanauts.
  - Aquanauts (The): Episode 17B, 1960 Nov 7 (Box 54)
    Working title: The Big Swim. In bound volume labeled The Aquanauts.
  - Aquanauts (The): Episode 8B, 1960 Aug 5 (Box 54)
    In bound volume labeled The Aquanauts.
  - Aquanauts (The): Killers in Paradise, 1960 Dec 1 (Box 27)
  - Banacek: Only One in the World (The), 1973 Oct 1 (Box 34)
    In bound volume labeled Banacek and McCloud.
  - Banacek: Only One in the World (The) - script drafts, 1973 Oct (Box 7)
  - Banyon: Good Night, Sweetheart, 1972 Aug 11 (Box 28)
  - Barnaby Jones: Sunday: Doomsday, 1972 Dec 21 (Box 28)
  - Bat Masterson: Stampede at Tent City, 1958 July 23 (Box 48)
    In bound volume labeled Random TV Scripts.
  - Bert D'Angelo, Superstar: Book of Fear (The), 1976 Feb 5 (Box 38)
    In bound volume labeled Bert D'Angelo/Superstar Volume 3.
  - Bert D'Angelo, Superstar: Brown Horse Connection (The), 1976 Jan 26 (Box 37)
    In bound volume labeled Bert D'Angelo/Superstar Volume 1.
  - Bert D'Angelo, Superstar: Concerned Citizen (A), 1976 Feb 23 (Box 37)
    In bound volume labeled Bert D'Angelo/Superstar Volume 2.
  - Bert D'Angelo, Superstar: Cops Who Sleep Together, 1975 Dec 22 (Box 37)
  - Bert D'Angelo, Superstar: Flannagan's Fleet, 1976 Mar 10 (Box 37)
  - Bert D'Angelo, Superstar: Men With No Past, 1976 Jan 16 (Box 37)
  - Bert D'Angelo, Superstar: Missing Link (The), 1975 Dec 16 (Box 37)
  - Bert D'Angelo, Superstar: Noise in the Street (The), 1976 Feb 3 (Box 37)
  - Bert D'Angelo, Superstar: Requiem For a Rip-off, 1976 Mar 4 (Box 37)
  - Bert D'Angelo, Superstar: Scag, 1976 Mar 29 (Box 38)
  - Bert D'Angelo, Superstar: Serpent's Tooth (The), 1976 Apr 5 (Box 38)
  - Bert D'Angelo, Superstar: What Kind of Cop Are You?, 1976 Mar 22 (Box 38)
  - Bob Hawk Original Animal Hour (The) (audition script), 1950 Jan 21 (Box 45)
  - Breaking Point: Better Than a Dead Lion, 1963 Nov 7 (Box 54)
    In bound volume labeled Breaking Point Vol. I.
  - Breaking Point: Child of the Center Ring (A), 1963 Dec 18 (Box 54)
  - Breaking Point: Confounding Her Astronomers, 1964 Feb 18 (Box 54)
    In bound volume labeled Breaking Point Vol. II.
  - Breaking Point: Devil On Two Sticks, 1963 Oct 30 (Box 54)
  - Breaking Point: Land More Cruel (A), 1963 Nov 26 (Box 54)
  - Breaking Point: My Hands Are Clean, 1964 Mar 3 (Box 54)
  - Breaking Point: Summer House (The), 1964 Jan 21 (Box 54)
  - Breaking Point: Tides of Darkness (The), 1964 Jan 15 (Box 54)
  - Calloway's Climb - screenplay, no date (Box 46)
  - Calloway's Climb: script drafts and preproduction notes, no date (Box 8)
  - Climax: Bigger They Come (The), 1954 Jan 6 (Box 34)
    In bound volume labeled Climax.
  - Climax: Epitaph for a Spy, 1954 Dec 9 (Box 34)
  - Climax: Leaf Out of the Book (A), 1955 Feb 3 (Box 34)
    In bound volume labeled Climax and Shower of Stars.
  - Climax: South of the Sun, 1955 Mar 3 (Box 34)
  - Climax: White Carnation (The), 1954 Dec 16 (Box 55)
  - Connection Terror script drafts, 1982 Jun and Aug (Box 19)
  - Connection: Terror!, 1982 June 14 (Box 46)
  - Crime Classics: Crime of Bathsheba Spooner (The), no date (Box 27)
  - Diamond Head: Nautilus Gambit (The) - pilot script, 1979 Oct 5 (Box 46)
  - Diamond Head: script drafts, no date (Box 20)
  - Dick Powell Show (The): Killer in the House, 1961 May 25 (Box 43)
  - Doc Elliot: Small Hand of Friendship (A), 1973 July 10 (Box 47)
  - Doctors Hospital: Sleepless With Pale Eyes, 1975 June 30 (Box 46)
  - Doctors Hospital: Sleepless, with Pale Eyes - script drafts, preproduction notes and treatment, 1975 May-Jun (Box 7)
  - Frankie and Johnny, no date (Box 47)
  - Girls From Menta (The), no date (Box 45)
  - Girls from Menta (The) concept and script drafts, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Grand Hotel: Sleepless, With Pale Eyes, 1963 Aug 13 (Box 47)
  - Greek Tycoon (The) script, no date (Box 11)
  - Greek Tycoon (The) script drafts, no date (Box 10)
  - Greek Tycoon (The) script drafts and interviews, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Hospital Story script, 1962 Feb 24 (Box 43)
  - Hospital Story: Episode 2, 1961 Oct 25 (Box 47)
  - I Spy: Blackout, 1966 Aug 10 (Box 53)
    In bound volume labeled I Spy, 1966-67, Volume 7.
  - I Spy: Casanova From Canarsie, 1966 Sept 22 (Box 53)
  - I Spy: Clippings and ephemera (2 folders), 1965-1967 (Box 62)
  - I Spy: Cops and Robbers, 1967 Jan 3 (Box 53)
  - I Spy: Night Train to Madrid, 1966 Nov 15 (Box 53)
  - Inhabitants of Venus (The), no date (Box 11)
  - Jonathan Croft script, 1962 Sept 19 (Box 47)
  - Jonathan Croft: Matter of Faith (A) - pilot script, 1962 Oct 22 (Box 47)
  - K.C. Adams pilot, 1981 Mar 16 (Box 46)
  - K.C. Adams script, no date (Box 11)
  - Kojak project magazine article (research), 1974 Apr 5 (Box 70)
  - Kojak: Knockover, 1973 Oct 2 (Box 36)
    In bound volume labeled Kojak Volume 1.
  - Kojak: Knockover - notes, no date (Box 66)
  - Kojak: Knockover - script drafts and treatment, 1973 Aug-Oct (Box 4)
  - Kojak: Knockover - treatment, 1973 Jul (Box 3)
  - Kojak: Kojak: Nicest Guys on the Block (The), 1975 Aug 14 (Box 36)
    In bound volume labeled Kojak Volume 2.
  - Kojak: Marker For a Dead Bookie, 1973 Dec 11 (Box 36)
  - Kojak: Marker to a Dead Bookie, 1973 Dec (Box 2)
  - Kojak: Mojo, 1974 Feb 25 (Box 36)
  - Kojak: Mojo script drafts, 1974 Feb (Box 3)
  - Kojak: Nice Guy in the Neighborhood (The) - script drafts, production notes and treatment, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Kojak: Secret Show, Deadly Snow - script drafts, preproduction notes and treatment, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Kojak: Secret Snow, Deadly Snow, 1974 Dec 16 (Box 36)
  - Kojak: Short Cut to Hell, 1977 Aug 5 (Box 36)
  - Kojak: Skag - script drafts, 1972 Nov (Box 4)
  - Kojak: Slay Ride, 1974 Jul 11 (Box 2)
  - Kojak: Slay Ride, 1974 July 11 (Box 36)
  - Kojak: Slay Ride - script drafts, preproduction notes and treatment, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Kojak: Unfair Trade (An), 1976 Aug 23 (Box 36)
  - Kojak: Unfair Trade (An) - script drafts, 1976 Aug (Box 2)
  - Kwai Lo, no date (Box 45)
  - Kwai Lo: script drafts and preproduction notes, no date (Box 8)
  - Law and Mr. Jones (The): Requiem For a Featherweight, 1962 Jan 19 (Box 47)
  - Mackenzie's Raiders: Long Day (The), 1958 July 25 (Box 48)
  - Manhunter (The): Death Watch, 1975 Jan 6 (Box 36)
    In bound volume labeled The Manhunter.
  - Manhunter (The): Seventh Man (The), 1974 Dec 16 (Box 36)
  - Manhunter (The): To Kill a Tiger, 1975 Jan 16 (Box 36)
  - Manhunter (The): Trial by Terror, 1975 Jan 24 (Box 36)
  - Manhunter (The): Wrong Man (The), 1974 Dec 26 (Box 36)
  - Mc Cloud: Death Takes a Number - preproduction notes, scene sequence and treatment, 1974 Mar (Box 2)
  - Mc Cloud: Shivaree on Delancey Street, 1974 June 18 (Box 34)
  - Mc Cloud: Shivaree on Delancy Street - script drafts and treatment, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Money on the Side, 1981 Sept 3 (Box 46)
  - Money on the Side: script drafts, 1981-1982 (Box 12)
  - Money on the Side: script drafts, no date (Box 13)
  - Most Deadly Game (The): Breakdown, 1970 Aug 20 (Box 35)
    In bound volume labeled The Most Deadly Game, 1970 Volume 2.
  - Most Deadly Game (The): Classic Burial Position (The), 1970 May 22 (Box 35)
    In bound volume labeled The Most Deadly Game, 1970 Volume 1.
  - Most Deadly Game (The): Gabrielle - teleplay, 1970 June 26 (Box 35)
  - Most Deadly Game (The): I, Said the Sparrow, 1970 June 18 (Box 35)
  - Most Deadly Game (The): Lady From Praha (The), 1970 Aug 12 (Box 35)
  - Most Deadly Game (The): Little David, 1970 June 30 (Box 35)
  - Most Deadly Game (The): Model for Murder, 1970 June 8 (Box 35)
  - Most Deadly Game (The): Nightbirds, 1970 June 16 (Box 35)
  - Most Deadly Game (The): Photo Finish, 1970 June 26 (Box 35)
  - Most Deadly Game (The): War Games, 1970 July 15 (Box 35)
  - Most Deadly Game (The): Who Killed Kindness, 1970 Sept 16 (Box 35)
  - Most Deadly Game (The): Witches' Sabbath, 1970 July 15 (Box 35)
  - Movin' On: Good Life (The), 1974 Sept 10 (Box 47)
  - Nakai: Beginning in the Wilderness (A), 1974 Sept 9 (Box 28)
  - Nakai: Beginning in the Wilderness (A) - script drafts and treatment, 1974 Jul-Aug (Box 6)
  - Nakai: Concept, no date (Box 6)
  - Nakai: Matter of Choice (A), 1974 Oct 11 (Box 28)
  - Nakai: Plant Evidence - script, 1974 Oct (Box 6)
  - Nakai: Trouble in Temescal, 1974 Nov 5 (Box 28)
  - Nakai: Troubled Time in Tesescal - script drafts and story outline, 1974 Oct (Box 6)
  - Nativity (The), 1978 June (Box 46)
  - Nativity: Final script drafts, 1978 Mar and Jun (Box 15)
  - Nativity: script drafts, notes and outline, no date (Box 14)
  - Night Watch (audition script), no date (Box 66)
  - Petracelli: Evil Men Do (The), 1974 Mar 13 (Box 47)
  - Petracelli: Evil Men Do (The) - script drafts and preproduction notes, 1974 Jan-Mar (Box 7)
  - Police Story (The): Violent and Lonely Place (A), 1973 Oct 22 (Box 47)
  - Police Story (The): Violent and Lonely Place (A) - script drafts, preproduction notes and treatment, 1973 Sep-Nov (Box 1)
  - Ryan: Hamlet's Horse, no date (Box 21)
  - Ryan: Mark of Miss Kane (The), no date (Box 21)
  - Ryan: Report In, Lieutenant Callison, no date (Box 21)
  - Ryan: Reviews of Ryan - Australian TV Drama, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Ryan: Slay Ride, no date (Box 21)
  - Shower of Stars: Burlesque, 1955 Mar 17 (Box 34)
  - Snoop Sisters (The): unsorted script materials, no date (Box 16)
  - Snoop Sisters (The): Which Wine Goes with Murder, no date (Box 66)
  - South Seas: Pentecost Island, no date (Box 27)
  - Streets of San Francisco: Face in a Book - preproduction notes, no date (Box 5)
  - Streets of San Francisco: False Witness, 1974 Sept 25 (Box 38)
    In bound volume labeled Streets of San Francisco.
  - Streets of San Francisco: False Witness - script drafts, preproduction notes and treatment, 1974 Jun-Aug (Box 5)
  - Streets of San Francisco: For Good or Evil, 1974 July 9 (Box 38)
  - Streets of San Francisco: For Good or Evil - script drafts, preproduction notes and treatment, 1974 Apr (Box 5)
  - Streets of San Francisco: Super Star - script drafts, preproduction notes and treatment, 1975 May and Jul (Box 5)
  - Streets of San Francisco: Superstar, 1975 July 7 (Box 38)
  - Streets of San Francisco: Tower Beyond Tragedy, 1972 July 17 (Box 38)
  - Streets of San Francisco: Unicorn (The) - teleplay, 1972 Nov 27 (Box 38)
  - Streets of San Francisco: Year of the Locusts (The) - synopsis, no date (Box 70)
  - Switch: Fifty Thousand Kopek Caper (The) - script and treatment, 1976 Jul (Box 1)
  - Switch: Fleece of Snow, 1976 July 15 (Box 46)
  - Switch: Fleece of Snow - script drafts and treatment, 1976 Jun-Jul (Box 1)
  - Switch: Hundred Thousand Ruble Rumble (The), 1976 Aug 13 (Box 46)
  - Switch: Hundred Thousand Rumble (The) - script drafts, 1976 Aug (Box 1)
  - Target: Assassin, 1958 Mar 11 (Box 48)
  - Target: Middlemen (The), 1961 Oct 4 (Box 27)
  - Target: Piano to Thunder Springs, 1958 July 24 (Box 48)
  - Thieves' Market, no date (Box 47)
  - Untitled script, no date (Box 48)
  - Virginian (The): Decision at Sundown, 1963 Jan 29 (Box 52)
    In bound volume labeled The Virginian.
  - Virginian (The): Executioners (The), 1962 May 17 (Box 52)
  - Virginian (The): Far and Fetching Sound (A), 1962 July 30 (Box 52)
  - Virginian (The): Woman From White Wing, 1962 May 14 (Box 52)
  - Woman With a Badge: Cooling Off - script, no date (Box 66)
- Motion Picture Projects, (1956-1957, 1963-1966, 1976-1983)
  There is no specific arrangement to the series.
  The series contains screenplays, clippings, and publicity materials related to film projects such as The Pawnbroker, Greek Tycoon, and The Next Man. Some of the scripts are in bound volumes and include production information.
  - Cabo Blanco - screenplay, 1979 Mar 13 (Box 32)
  - Capitol Offense - screenplay, 1956 June 14 (Box 24)
  - Fool Killer (The) - clippings, 1963 Jan 23 (Box 70)
  - Fool Killer (The) - screenplay, 1963 Apr 25 (Box 70)
  - Greek Tycoon (The) - clippings and script cover (3 folders), 1978 (Box 62)
  - Greek Tycoon (The) - publicity, c. 1978 (Box 64)
  - Greek Tycoon (The) - screenplay, no date (Box 52)
  - Handle With Care - script and production information, 1957 Sept 9 (Box 33)
  - Hot Summer Night - screenplay, 1956 June 14 (Box 32)
  - Next Man (The) - clippings, 1976 (Box 62)
  - Next Man (The) - screenplay, 1976 Jan 27 (Box 70)
  - Paul Bryant, the Bear, 1983 Nov 17 (Box 50)
  - Pawnbroker (The) - clippings and ephemera (3 folders), 1965-1966 (Box 62)
  - Pawnbroker (The) - script and production information, 1963 Aug 28 (Box 32)
  - That Championship Season, no date (Box 18)
  - That Championship Season - screenplay, no date (Box 31)
- Project Files, (1947-1989)
  The series includes script material, notes, outlines, and treatments for both produced and unproduced projects. Additionally, there are a small amount clippings, articles, and interviews which may have been used as research for film and television projects.
  - Act of Love, no date (Box 61)
  - Adios, O'Callahan - screenplay treatment outline, no date (Box 60)
  - Armies of the Night (The), 1969 (Box 61)
  - Australia Letters, no date (Box 50)
  - Avila Gold (The) - screenplay, 1975 Aug 26 (Box 52)
  - Avila Gold (The) - screenplay, 1975 Aug 26 (Box 31)
  - Avila Gold (The): script materials and synopsis, 1975 Aug (Box 17)
  - Blessed McGill, no date (Box 35)
  - Blessed McGill (2 folders), 1969 Jan (Box 51)
  - Blessed McGill (3 folders), 1969 Feb, no date (Box 50)
  - Bodyguard (The), 1974 Sept - Oct (Box 60)
  - Bowling Ball Romance (The), no date (Box 51)
  - Broadway #60, no date (Box 52)
  - Brother I Always Wanted (The), no date (Box 61)
  - Cannon, 1973 May 3 (Box 60)
    Lady Under Water.
  - Case History - article for reference, no date (Box 66)
  - Cassette tapes, no date (Box 65)
    May be related to interview transcripts in box 42. Restricted access: Audio materials in this collection are restricted and require advance notice for use.
  - Children of Sliska (The), no date (Box 67)
  - Clues, 1975 Nov (Box 60)
  - Constantia, no date (Box 51)
    Also labeled Act of Love.
  - Danny and Rover - screenplay notes, no date (Box 66)
  - Defoe - pilot script, 1972 Jan 4 (Box 36)
    Sapphire Tears (The).
  - Denmark - correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 61)
    See also files tilted The Game.
  - Denmark (The Game) (2 folders), 1984-1988 (Box 48)
  - Denmark Letters, 1982-1985 (Box 61)
  - Diamondhead, 1979 Oct 29 (Box 57)
  - Doc Elliot, 1973 May (Box 60)
  - Double Trouble - Kleiner script, 1971 Sept 26 (Box 56)
  - Double Trouble (2 folders), 1971 (Box 55)
  - Early Sorrow - radio script, no date (Box 68)
  - Easterwood Park - clippings, no date (Box 61)
  - Evil Men Do (The), 1982 May (Box 57)
  - Evil That Men Do script drafts, 1982 May (Box 19)
  - Fiji, 1974 May 6 (Box 62)
  - First Ward (The), no date (Box 52)
  - For Operation Danger (First Nighter Reject), no date (Box 66)
  - Frankie and Johnny, no date (Box 66)
  - Frankie and Johnny, no date (Box 51)
  - Game, c. 1988 (Box 52)
    See also files titled Denmark.
  - Game (The) (2 folders), no date, c. 1987 (Box 61)
  - Glow (The) - synopsis, notes, no date (Box 57)
  - Go an Extra Mile first draft, 1980 Dec 17 (Box 16)
  - Go an Extra Mile, 1980 Dec 17 (Box 57)
  - Gold of Malabar (The) (4 folders), 1969 Feb - May (Box 51)
  - Hawaii 5-0 - treatment, no date (Box 56)
  - Hot Summer Night - sheet music, c. 1956, no date (Box 62)
  - Hunt and Peck, no date (Box 60)
  - I Spy, no date (Box 52)
  - Island - television series treatment, no date (Box 60)
  - Island - treatment, no date (Box 51)
  - It's a Capitol Life - television treatment, no date (Box 66)
  - Johnny Madero (2 folders), 1947 July 2, no date (Box 61)
  - Jonathan Croft (2 folders), 1991 Oct 31, no date (Box 68)
  - K.C. Adams - pilot script, no date (Box 57)
  - Knight's Gambit, 1982 Feb 14 (Box 57)
  - Korczak, Janusz material (2 folders), 1984 (Box 67)
    Appears related to The Children of Sliska.
  - Kwai Lo, no date (Box 56)
  - Lady and the Cop (The), no date (Box 61)
  - Last Game (The) - treatment copies, 1986 Sept 19 (Box 48)
  - Laura, no date (Box 67)
  - Ma Paree - story outline, 1962 Apr 3 (Box 66)
  - Model War, no date (Box 57)
  - Money Man (The), 1973 (Box 55)
  - Money Man (The), no date (Box 61)
  - Money Man (The) - correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 70)
  - Movin' On, 1974 June (Box 59)
  - Mr. Cheyney's Autumn (Box 62)
  - Mulcahy, no date (Box 67)
    Appears related to The Qaddafi Connection.
  - Music industry related clippings, notes, and interview transcripts (4 folders), 1977-1978 (Box 63)
    Could be research; appears related to Rhinestone Cowboy. Interview transcripts may be related to Cassettes in box 44.
  - Name plate and address book, no date (Box 61)
  - New Adventures of Michael Shayne (The), 1948 Feb 16 (Box 48)
  - Next Man (The), no date (Box 55)
  - Notions, 1975 (Box 55)
  - Old Spies Never Die - treatment, no date (Box 56)
  - Old Spies Never Die: script drafts, 1979 Jul and Nov (Box 16)
  - Operation Terror (4 folders), 1982 Apr, Aug (Box 57)
  - Palance, 1980 Oct 27 (Box 56)
  - Palance: nsorted script materials, no date (Box 16)
  - Paradise Cove, 1970 Aug (Box 61)
  - Paradise Cove - television treatment, 1961 Feb 9 (Box 68)
  - Paul Bryant, the Bear (4 folders), 1981-1984 (Box 56)
  - Picket Productions, no date (Box 60)
  - Pin Stripe Pagliacci (J. Cotton), 1948 (Box 68)
  - Play With Me, no date (Box 55)
  - Play With Me - treatment, no date (Box 60)
  - Plots - F. Sherwood, no date (Box 50)
  - Police Story (The), 1973 July - Aug (Box 60)
  - Pray With Me, no date (Box 55)
  - Probe, 1972 June 5 (Box 60)
    With This Ring.
  - Pros (The), 1971 (Box 55)
    Originally in folder labeled Cops Under Psychological Stress.
  - Pros (The) - treatment, 1971 Dec 22 (Box 62)
  - Publicity (3 folders), 1950s-1960s (Box 63)
    Clippings and trade publications; some related to Fine and Friedkin.
  - Qaddafi Connection (The), no date (Box 67)
  - Rhinestone Cowboy, 1978 (Box 61)
    See also file titled: Music industry related clippings, notes, and interview transcripts.
  - Rhinestone Cowboy - screenplay, 1978 Dec 12 (Box 57)
  - Rhinestone Cowboy - treatment, 1978 (Box 63)
  - Rhinestone Cowboy: script drafts, no date (Box 20)
  - Richie, Lance, and Alvin - ideas for series, no date (Box 68)
  - Rip Off - treatment, 1973 Oct (Box 60)
  - Saturday Night Special, 1972 Sept 20 (Box 60)
  - Scarlet Queen, 1947 Sept 25 (Box 50)
    Shore Leave and the Unhappy Wife.
  - Scrapbook of clippings related to Barbara Graham, 1953 Oct (Box 64)
  - Script - unidentified project, no date (Box 61)
    Appears related to Gold of Malabar.
  - Some Sisters of Eve, 1981 Mar 27 (Box 35)
  - Story ideas, 1969 June, no date (Box 67)
  - Streets of San Francisco - script pages, 1974 Oct (Box 52)
    False Witness.
  - Surrogates (The), no date (Box 60)
  - Suspense, 1951 Dec 10 (Box 52)
    Blackjack to Kill.
  - They Shoot Horses, Don't They?, no date (Box 50)
  - Thompson, Luke, 1982 (Box 67)
  - Three to Go, 1974 Apr 24 (Box 63)
  - Trapped Down Under - pilot script, 1972 Aug 21 (Box 62)
  - Treatments - various projects, 1972-1973 (Box 60)
  - Two Musketeers (The), 1974-1975 (Box 60)
  - Two Musketeers (The), no date (Box 56)
  - Typescript notes, no date (Box 61)
    Some related to Banyon.
  - Untitled television project - notes, 1981 Sept 14 (Box 52)
    Potentially to be titled Walbrook or Easterwood Park.
  - Voyage of the Scarlet Queen, 1947 Aug 14 (Box 52)
  - Voyage of the Scarlet Queen, 1947 Aug 28 (Box 51)
  - Walbrook, 1981 (Box 55)
  - Wanderers, no date (Box 63)
  - Where in the World - treatment, 1972 Jan 9 (Box 62)
  - Whistler (The), [1947] (Box 68)
  - Yankee Drummer, no date (Box 51)
- Business Records, 1969, 1974-1981, 1984
  The Business Records includes correspondence and agreements. There is also a small amount of general financial information relating to pension and profit sharing plans.
  - Agency agreements, 1979-1981 (Box 59)
  - Cabo Blanco, 1979 (Box 58)
  - Code Name Diamondhead, 1979-1980 (Box 58)
  - Correspondence, 1969, 1978 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence and agreements, 1978, 1980-1981 (Box 56)
  - Dejar, Inc. - correspondence, 1977-1986 (Box 58)
  - Dejar, Inc. - pension plan, 1982-1984 (Box 58)
  - Frank Costello project, 1978 (Box 58)
  - Friedkin and Fine Productions - profit sharing plan, 1977 (Box 59)
  - Go An Extra Mile, 1981 (Box 58)
  - Halmi Deal, 1977-1981 (Box 67)
  - Halmi, Robert, 1977, 1984 (Box 59)
  - High Point, 1979 (Box 58)
  - I Spy, 1977 (Box 58)
  - Immortal Pediatrician (The), 1980 (Box 58)
  - K.C. Adams, 1981 (Box 59)
  - Money on the Side, 1981-1982 (Box 58)
    Also referred to as Housewife Prostitutes.
  - Nativity (The), 1978 (Box 58)
  - Next Man (The), 1978-1980 (Box 59)
  - Paul Bryant, the Bear, 1984 (Box 59)
  - Qaddafi Connection (The), 1984 (Box 59)
  - Rhinestone Cowboy, 1978, 1981 (Box 59)
  - That Championship Season, 1977, 1983 (Box 58)
  - Two Musketeers (The) - agreements, 1974 Oct - 1975 Jan (Box 70)
  - Writers Guild of America - registration information and royalty statements, 1974 Apr, June (Box 70)
- Unidentified Projects, (1957, 1969, 1970s)
  Files are arranged alphabetically by titles.
  Unidentified Projects includes scripts and screenplays that are not identified as being created for motion picture, television or radio; and it is unknown if they were produced.
  - Back Game draft, 1975 Oct 24 (Box 8)
  - Blessed McGill - screenplay, no date (Box 33)
  - Children of Sliska - script, no date (Box 26)
  - Confidential: Liz, no date (Box 21)
  - Confidential: Miss Ogilvie Reports, no date (Box 21)
  - Confidential: Sixth of June Doesn't Rhyme (The), no date (Box 21)
  - Division 4: Come Play with Me, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Forum for Contemporary History (Newsletter/journal/letter publication), 1973-1974 (Box 67)
  - Gold of Malabar - screenplay, 1969 June 12 (Box 37)
  - Highpoint - screenplay, no date (Box 32)
  - Kahlil draft, 1975 Oct 16 (Box 8)
  - Now Are the Heroes - screenplay, 1969 (Box 33)
  - Phoenix of Sliska 9 script drafts, no date (Box 20)
  - Prime Minister (The) - screenplay, 1978 May 19 (Box 31)
  - Prime Minister (The) draft and notes, no date (Box 17)
  - Prisoner in Paradise - script, 1957 May (Box 33)
  - Shadow on the Land final draft, 1967 Nov 17 (Box 16)
    Aslo known as Teeth of the Dragon.
  - Shannon, no date (Box 11)
  - Trapped/ Down Under revised script, 1972 Aug 21 (Box 21)
- Short stories, Articles, and Other Writings, 1945-1948
  The files are arranged alphabetically by titles.
  The series includes a number of short stories and article drafts; many are undated. Additionally there is an unidentified typescript manuscript as well as typed pages from other writing projects.
  - And They Shall Inherit Whatever's Left - short story, no date (Box 68)
  - Army Rehabilitates the Hard-of-Hearing Soldier (The) - article, [1946] (Box 68)